Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Missouri, 1906-1912; 5
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:24)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:25)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:26)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:27)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:28)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:29)
  - Missouri: River Scene with Railroad Bridge, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:30)
  - Missouri: Railroad Depot, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:31)
  - Missouri: Wooden Railroad Bridge Over Water, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:32)
  - Missouri: Railroad Derailment, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:33)
  - Missouri: Rural Road, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:34)
  - Missouri: Unidentified People and Location x 6, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:35)
  - Missouri: Missouri: Unidentified People and Location x 6, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:36)
  - Missouri: St. Louis 792-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-792.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:37)
  - Missouri: Railroad: General, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:38)
  - Missouri: Railroad Depot 905-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-905.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:39)
  - Missouri: Industry: Steam Engine Room 753-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-753.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:40)
  - Missouri: Remains of Brick Building, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:41)
  - Missouri: Unidentified Building or Courthouse, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:42)
  - Missouri: Chautagua Assembly, Dexter, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:43)
  - Missouri: River Scene with Boat, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:44)
  - Missouri: River Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:45)
  - Missouri: Man Working, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:46)
  - Missouri: Street Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:47)
  - Missouri: Street Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:48)
  - Missouri: Lake Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:49)
  - Missouri: Unidentified Building, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:50)
  - Missouri: Grayridge, Store Complex, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:51)
  - Missouri: Unidentified Theatre Interior, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:52)
  - Missouri: Unidentified Lake, Man and House, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:53)
  - Missouri: Unidentified Lake and Dam, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:54)
  - Missouri: Boating Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:55)
  - Missouri: Wood and Steel Bridge, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:56)
  - Missouri: Windmill and Farmhouse, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:57)
  - Missouri: River with House and Windmill, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:58)
  - Missouri: Crowd Scene Near Covered Area, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:59)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 754-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-754.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:60)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 754-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-754.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:61)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 755-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-755.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:62)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 784-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-784.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:63)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 755-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-755.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:64)
  - Missouri: Circus Scene 755-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-755.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:65)
  - Missouri: Store Interior: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-924.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:66)
- Transportation, circa 1900s-1920s; 6
  This series contains images of aircraft, automobiles, street cars, wagons or carriages, and watercraft including steamships, river boats, sailboats, and ferries. Several examples of early steam powered water vessels are represented. One better known example is a photograph of the passenger steamship "Eastland," included in this collection.
  Related Resources
  Related references
  Young, David, "The Eastland disaster: A summer excursion turns into the worst accident in the annals of Great Lakes shipping." Chicago Tribune (Chicago, Ill), undated. Accessed December 28, 2013.
  Watercraft: The passenger steam ship "Eastland" is shown in this image. On July 24, 1915, while docked in Chicago, Illinois, for departure on a cruise to Michigan City, Indiana, it rolled over onto its side causing passengers to be thrown into the water. This tipping or listing of the vessel began after the 2,573 passengers had boarded. This accident claimed the lives of 844 men, women, and children. It is reported the incident caused the largest number of deaths in any single event in the continental U.S. in the twentieth century. Digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-792.1.tif. The picture was taken circa 1906 by E.C. Blomeyer when the vessel was operated
  Watercraft: The riverboat "Grey Eagle" in Missouri. Its destination plaques read: "St. Louis-Cape Girardeau." Digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-779.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: People wait or watch a large steamship off in the distance. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-786.3.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
  Watercraft: A river ferry carries passengers in this scene most likely taken somewhere in Missouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-947.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: Steamship "Quantico" with tender at an unidentified port. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-817.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910
  Autos: An unknown group pile into an auto for a ride. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-764.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912
  This scene shows carriages and wagons at an event taken most likely in Missouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-913.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1906
  Aircraft: A Wright Brothers Model B is shown in an unspecified location, possibly San Antonio, Texas. Notice the two clamps repairing the lower left wing tip's edge. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-499.3.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: The steamship "Chequamegon," of the Pabst Brewing Company's White Fish Bay Resort. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-778.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1906
  Aircraft: A Wright Brothers Model B is shown in an unspecified location, possibly San Antonio, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-499.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: An empty river ferry and tender stand empty in this scene most likely in Missouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-947.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: A large unidentified steamship fills the air as it approaches. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-947.3.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Autos: This early bus photograph was taken in an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-922.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Watercraft: Steam powered river boats line up at an unidentified location. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-817.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910
  Autos: This large automobile was photographed in Misssouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-783.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910
  - Transportation: Airplane: Wright Brothers Model B, 506-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-506.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:1)
  - Transportation: Airplane: Wright Brothers Model B, 506-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-506.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:2)
  - Transportation: Airplane: Wright Brothers Model B, 506-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-506.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:3)
  - Transportation: Airplane, 499-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-499.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:4)
  - Transportation: Airplane, 499-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-499.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:5)
  - Transportation: Automobile, 756-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-756.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:6)
  - Transportation: Automobile, 783-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-783.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:7)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 778-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-778.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:8)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 694-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-694.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:9)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 889-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-889.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:10)
  - Transportation: Automobile, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:11)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 516-1: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-516.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:12)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 516-2: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-516.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:13)
  - Transportation: Automobile, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:14)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 896-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-896.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:15)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 897-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-897.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:16)
  - Transportation: Automobile: 764-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-764.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:17)
  - Transportation: Automobile, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:18)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship 947-3: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-947.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:19)
  - Transportation: Missouri River Ferry 947-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-947.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:20)
  - Transportation: Missouri River Ferry 947-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-947.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:21)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship 778-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-778.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:22)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship 792-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-792.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:23)
  - Transportation: Ships: Paddle Steamer 779: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-779.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:24)
  - Transportation: Ships 788-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-788.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:25)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship: 787-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-787.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:26)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship with Passengers Waiting 786-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-786.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:27)
  - Transportation: Ships: 804-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-804.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:28)
  - Transportation: Ships: 804-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-804.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:29)
  - Transportation: Ships: Sailboat and people, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:30)
  - Transportation: Ships: Boat in Dry Dock, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:31)
  - Transportation: Ships: Sailboat, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6:32)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:33)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamship in Dock 817-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-817.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:34)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamships: Quantico: 817-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-817.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:35)
  - Transportation: Ships: Steamships: Quantico: Digital ID: 817-2: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-817.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:36)
  - Transportation: Ships: Tugboat: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-816.5.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:37)
  - Transportation: Ships: Unidentified x10, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:38)
  - Transportation: Galveston?: Open-Air Bus 922-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-922.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:39)
  - Transportation: Wagons 913-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-913.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:40)
  - Transportation: Wagons, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:41)
  - Transportation: Wagons 911-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-911.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:42)
  - Transportation: Train Station: Unidentified Location, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:43)
  - Transportation: Street Car: Sapulpa, OK.: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-transp-780.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6:44)
- Agriculture, 1900s-1920s; 7
  This subseries contains images of ranching and crop-raising. Included are livestock such as cattle, goats, pigs, and chickens. The crop scenes show fields and an early water irrigation system. Locations are not certain, but it is believed that most are of Texas with some images taken in Missouri.
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:1)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:2)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:3)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:4)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-5: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.5.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:5)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 800-6: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-800.6.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:6)
  - Agriculture: Chickens, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:7)
  - Agriculture: Chickens, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:8)
  - Agriculture: Crops, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:9)
  - Agriculture: Chicken or Pheasants, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:10)
  - Agriculture: Horses or Mules, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7:11)
  - Agriculture: Crops 892-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-892.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:12)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 895-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-895.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:13)
  - Agriculture: Cattle 900-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-900.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:14)
  - Agriculture: Cattle, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:15)
  - Agriculture: Crops-Water Irrigation 888-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-888.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:16)
  - Agriculture: Crops 888-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-888.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:17)
  - Agriculture: Goats, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:18)
  - Agriculture: Goats, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:19)
  - Agriculture: Goats, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:20)
  - Agriculture: Fenced in Areas for Livestock 879-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-879.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:21)
  - Agriculture: Unloading Pigs 881-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-881.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:22)
  - Agriculture: Farm Workers 894-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-894.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:23)
  - Agriculture: Silos or Food Storage Units: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-882.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:24)
  - Agriculture: Farm Workers with Truck: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-901.1.tif, 1917 November 29 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:25)
  - Agriculture: Workers Unloading Pigs: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-agric-899.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:26)
  - Agriculture: Field of Crops, 1906-1920 (Folder 7:27)
  - Agriculture: Field of Crops, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:28)
  - Agriculture: Cattle, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7:29)
  - Printed Photographs: (1 of 3), 1900s-1920s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Printed Photographs: (2 of 3), 1900s-1920s (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Printed Photographs: (3 of 3), 1900s-1920s (Box 7, Folder 8)
- General, 1900s-1920s; 8
  This series of photographs consists of several small combined groups such as unidentified homes, rugs, photos taken for publications, and animals such as birds and horn toads. The publication photographs were sent to Popular Mechanics Magazine, for stories written about filing photographic negatives, organizing hand tools, and home improvement.
  Blomeyer, Edward Charles. "Filing Prints and Negatives in Card Cabinet." Popular Mechanics Magazine, January 1919.
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Interior, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:1)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Exterior, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:2)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Exterior in Wooded Area, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:3)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Driveway with Car, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:4)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Interior Den, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:5)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Exterior with People and Autos, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:6)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Exterior-Porch, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:7)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Side View, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:8)
  - General: Homes: Blomeyer Residence in Waco?, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:9)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified Backyard of Home, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:10)
  - General: Homes: Unidentified-Interior, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:11)
  - General: Country Road and a Railroad Crossing, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:12)
  - General: Unidentified Tree-Lined Road, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:13)
  - General: Public Utilities Worker with Pump on Street, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:14)
  - General: Teddy Bear with a Rose, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:15)
  - General: Rolls of Material and Easels, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:16)
  - General: Rug on Easel, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:17)
  - General: Unknown Plant in Garden 883-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-883.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:18)
  - General: Unknown Monument, 1918 February 24 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:19)
  - General: Unidentified Building-Fire Station?, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:20)
  - General: Unidentified Building, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:21)
  - General: Unidentified Commercial Building 816-12: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-816.12.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:22)
  - General: Unidentified Building Ruins, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:23)
  - General: Popular Mechanics Magazine Submission Photos: "Photo Negative Filing and Storage" 508-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-508.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:24)
  - General: Popular Mechanics Magazine Submission Photo: Story on Sinks/Plumbing, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:25)
  - General: Popular Mechanics Magazine Submission Photo: Story on Organizing Hand Tools, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:26)
  - General: Texas Horn Toad 950-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-950.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:27)
  - General: Caged Parrot and Cat in Yard, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:28)
  - General: Caged Birds in Zoo, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:29)
  - General: Texas Horn Toad, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:30)
  - General: Texas Horn Toad, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:31)
  - General: Scenic View of Unknown Town, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:32)
  - General: Unidentified Woman with Flower Bouquet 805-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-805.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:33)
  - General: Unknown River, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:34)
  - General: Unknown Creek, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:35)
  - General: Miller Beer Factory: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-922.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8:36)
  - General: Architectural Renderings: Sports Field, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8:37)
  - Printed Photographs: General, 1900-1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Printed Photographs: General, 1900-1920 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Printed Photographs: E.C. Blomeyer Publication Submissions, 1910s-1920s (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Printed Photographs: Homes, 1900s-1920s (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Printed Photographs: Texas Horned Lizard, 1912-1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)